quiz1= [
	{
	 question: "What is the most common computer language?",
	 options: ["Java","R","Python","C++"],
	 answer: "Java"

 },
 {
	 question: "Public static void (what goes in here)",
	 options: ["String[]args","String args[]","Boolean [args]","String[args]"],
	 answer:"String[]args"

 },
 {
	question: "what is the size of a double variable?",
	options: ["8bit","16bit","32bit","64bit"],
	answer: "64bit"

 },
 {
	question: "What is the default value of byte variable?",
	options: ["0","0.0","null","undefined"],
	answer: "0"

 },
 {
	question: "Which method must be implemented by all threads?",
	options: ["run()","wait()","start()","wait()"],
	answer: "run()"

 },
 {
	question: "Which of the following creates a List of 3 visible items and multiple selections abled?",
	options: ["new List(false, 3)","new List(3, true)","new List(true, 3)","new List(3, false)"],
	answer: "new List(3, true)"

 },

 {
	question: "Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?",
	options: ["It has only methods","Objects can't be created","It has a fixed class name","It has no class name"],
	answer: "It has no class name"

 },
 {
	question: "Which package contains the Random class?",
	options: ["java.util package","java.lang package","java.awt package","java.io package"],
	answer: "java.util package"

 },
 {
	question: " which memory a String is stored, when we create a string using new operator?",
	options: ["Stack","String memory","Heap memory","Random storage space"],
	answer: "Heap memory"

 },
 {
	question: "What is the initial quantity of the ArrayList list?",
	options: ["5","10","0","100"],
	answer: "10"

 },
 {
	question: "Which of the following is a mutable class in java?",
	options: ["java.lang.String","java.lang.Byte","ava.lang.Short","java.lang.StringBuilder"],
	answer: "java.lang.StringBuilder"

 },
 {
	question: "How many threads can be executed at a time?",
	options: ["Only one thread","Multiple threads","Only main (main() method) thread","Two threads"],
	answer: "Multiple threads"

 },
 {
	question: "What does html stand for?",
	options: ["Home Tool Markup Language","Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language","Hyper Text Markup Language","html"],
	answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language"

 },
 {
	question: "What is the correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage?",
	options: ["Head, Title, HTML","Title, Head, HTML","HTML, Head, Title","head shoulders knees and toes"],
	answer: "HTML, Head, Title"

 },
 {
	question: " What is the correct HTML tag for inserting a line break?",
	options: ["Br","Break","Lb","bk"],
	answer: "Br"

 },
 {
	question: "How can you make a list that lists the items with numbers?",
	options: ["Ol","Dl","Ul","List"],
	answer: "Ol"

 },
 {
	question: "which course is this?",
	options: ["CUS1163","CUS1189","CUS1116","CUS1172"],
	answer: "CUS1172"

 },
 {
	question: "Which type  would you use to declare a number with a decimal ",
	options: ["long","int","String","double"],
	answer: "double"

 },
 {
	question: "Trick question: how much did you enjoy this?",
	options: ["alot ","loved it","loved it^2","a,b,& c"],
	answer: "a,b,& c"

 }
 ]
"Madrid",
"San Juan"
],
"answer": 2
},
{
"question": "What are the school colors of the University of Texas at Austin?",
"options": [
"Black, Red",
"Blue, Orange",
"White, Burnt Orange",
"White, Old gold, Gold"
],
"answer": 2
},
{
"question": "What is 70 degrees Fahrenheit in Celsius?",
"option": [
"18.8889",
"20",
"21.1111",
"158"
],
"answer": 2
},
{
"question": "When was Mahatma Gandhi born?",
"options": [
"October 2, 1869",
"December 15, 1872",
"July 18, 1918",
"January 15, 1929"
],
"answer": 0
},
{
"question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
"options": [
"7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
"86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
"238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
"35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)"
],
"answer": 2
},
{
"question": "What is 65 times 52?",
"options": [
"117",
"3120",
"3380",
"3520"
],
"answer": 2
},
{
"question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
"options": [
"6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
"7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
"19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
"29,029 ft (8,847 m)"
],
"answer": 3
},
{
"question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
"options": [
"May 2, 2008",
"May 4, 2012",
"May 3, 2013",
"April 4, 2014"
],
"answer": 1
},
{
"question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
"options": [
"0x18C1",
"0xBEEF",
"0xDEAD",
"0x12D591"
],
"answer": 1
}
]
}
